

#### **CONTACT**



7304 Riverchase Trail Denton, Texas 76210



kristi.a.taylor@me.com



www.taylorkristi.github.io



(903) 714-0221

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**PYTHON** 

**BOOTSTRAP** 

**ILLUSTRATOR** 

PHOTOSHOP

### SOCIAL



www.linkedin.com/in/kristitaylor



github.com/taylorkristi

# KRISTI TAYLOR

Front End Web Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

I love creating functional web products that are user-centered with rock-solid code.

And I'm conscientious, fast-learner-I round out my technical skills with a unique professional background in information science. That means I understand the bigger picture, too – how design, UX, and code work together to create unique web experiences.

# **RECENT PROJECTS**

2018 Denton Area Running Club Concept and Redesign -Co-developed a vibrant, secure website for this vibrant and community-driven running club from style concepts to end-product. Project is ongoing.

2018 Knob Hills Trail Race Concept and Redesign

Developed a website for annual trail race hosted by Denton Area Running Club that includes an integrated calendar and a minimal one-page design.

## **EDUCATION**

2018 FRONT END DEVELOPER NANODEGREE

Udacity (Google Developer Challenge Scholarship) expected Summer 2018

2013 MASTERS OF ART IN TEACHING

Texas Woman's University

2009 MASTERS OF LIBRARY SCIENCE

University of North Texas

2006 BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH

University of Texas at Tyler

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2014 - PRESENT LEWISVILLE ISD | LIBRARY MEDIA SPECIALIST

2013 - 2014 PLANO ISD | 7TH GRADE ENGLISH TEACHER

2007 - 2013 BARNES AND NOBLE BOOKSELLERS | MANAGER